

VATTSAL BHATT

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

vatsbhatt333@gmail.com +91 8000245312 Ahmedabad, GJ LinkedIn: Vattsal Bhatt

Github: Vattsal Bhatt

EDUCATION

Full-Stack Web Development

Masai School, Bangalore Oct 2021 - Present

B.Com (First Class)

New LJ College, Ahmedabad June 2018

SKILLS

HTML | CSS | Javascript | ExpressJS | Figma | AWS | Bootstrap

CERTIFICATION & LICENSES

NoCode Mentorship Program, GrowthSchool, 2021

SQL Basics Workshop Masai School, 2021

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

Theatre Competition Winner

Youth Fest and Rangayana, 2018

Content Creator

Self-Improvement Category, Instagram and YouTube

SOFT SKILLS

Flexible work approach | Leadership | Time-Management | Creativity | Self-Improvement

INTERESTS

Cinematography | Blockchain | Sports | Podcast | Reading | Finance | Music

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

An enthusiastic Full-stack web developer with hands-on experience in leading, developing & managing projects. Highly skilled decision-maker and problem solver with a specialization in Data Structure and algorithms. Looking forward to working as a developer and building interactive projects with a purposedriven organization.

PROJECTS

Steve Madden Clone



Features:

- REST APIs
- Search Functionality, and sorting APIs
- Filter and Sorting feature based on product type and price
- Dynamic Cart and Checkout page
- Razorpay payment gateway

Tech Stack: HTML | CSS | Javascript | Bootstrap | ExpressJS

Areas of Responsibility:

- Led the team and strategized tasks and responsibilities
- Developed and assembled two navbars for different screens
- · Found bugs in the original website and resolved them in the clone
- Built a responsive landing page
- Merged all the pages and ensured that the project was completed before time
- Resolved technical issues
- A collaborative project built by a team of 6 executed in 5 days.

Big Basket Clone 🖫



- A web application to order groceries.

Features:

- Responsive website
- · Sorting feature based on price
- Dynamic Cart page
- Add Product functionality

Tech Stack: HTML | CSS | Javascript

Areas of Responsibility:

- Led the team and completed the project before time
- Allocated tasks and monitored progress
- · Built the Landing and dynamic Cart page
- Resolved all bugs and assembled all the pages
- Designed the website according to optimal user experience
- -A collaborative project built by a team of 6 executed in 4 days.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Founder, PhotoGreen and Negast

June 2019 - Aug 2021

Areas of Responsibility:

- Built products with developers
- Created marketing strategies for downloads
- Onboarded vendors for sales
- Monitored operations
- Solved software and managerial issues

Manager, Shree Sagar Sales (Achieved 5x Growth)

June 2018 - Aug 2021

Areas of Responsibility:

- Increased sales with effective strategies
- Managed inventory
- Assessed customer needs to develop strategies
- Offered after-sales support to consumers